<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en-US">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="Well, child counselors treat a variety of issues. For instance, they treat children who have experienced trauma or upsetting events like the loss of a parent, pet, loved one, siblings, home, etc. And, they also treat children, who have witnessed or experienced abuse and/or intimidation. Basically, child counselors treat any issues that cause children social or emotional distress and/or any mental health condition that is affecting a child’s life. The goal of these professionals is to help your child identify and cope with any issue or issues they are experiencing in a healthy way.Adolescents express emotional distress differently from adults. Although parents were once kids themselves, their perspective in dealing with seemingly erratic behavior is often through the lens of an adult.Individual counseling is a one-on-one discussion between the counselor and the client. The two form an alliance, relationship or bond that enables trust and personal growth. During individual therapy sessions, patients and therapists form partnerships. Together, they work toward solving problems and achieving goals. Each session may not be a pleasant experience. It’s normal for frustrations and painful memories to surface during therapy. Even with these sensitive moments, therapists work to promote a safe and comfortable atmosphere where individuals can share thoughts.Issues such as divorce, financial hardship, death, or a mental health concern impact everyone in the family. Therapy can benefit families when these stressful events put a strain on relationships within the unit. Our Houston behavioral health services promote using this effective form of therapy to make the family stronger.The good news is that with relationship counseling, you and your partner can learn to identify and break the negative communication cycle that’s developed.  Our relationship therapists are experts at helping you identify and explore your communication patterns.  In the therapy room, you and your counselor will take a closer look at your relationship.  You’ll begin to identify the negative patterns in your relationship that you and your partner would like to change. After you have a clear picture of these patterns, you and your spouse can begin to make change in your relationship with the support of your couples therapist.">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logo-19053-black-1536x1518.png"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
.cbe9260185384bcc7fb0bdd5e87cb0d63 p,.cbe9260185384bcc7fb0bdd5e87cb0d63 a,.cbe9260185384bcc7fb0bdd5e87cb0d63 span,.cbe9260185384bcc7fb0bdd5e87cb0d63 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.u96c3ff16fdf21a146e7c2a0ab01823ce a{
font-size:16px;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:7.6px;
padding-right:8px;
padding-top:5px;
padding-bottom:5.4px;
}
.v2f279d878e8059c8ff2123028bc7a233{
background-color:#964e4e!important;
border-color:#964e4e!important;
color:#ffffff!important;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
.u96c3ff16fdf21a146e7c2a0ab01823ce p,.u96c3ff16fdf21a146e7c2a0ab01823ce span,.u96c3ff16fdf21a146e7c2a0ab01823ce label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.cbe9260185384bcc7fb0bdd5e87cb0d63 a,.u96c3ff16fdf21a146e7c2a0ab01823ce a{
color:#080808!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
footer{
background:#3d3d3d;
color:#ffffff;
}
.x215b9a4058c2f43277398a98099255d9:hover{
box-shadow: 0 49.9px 49.8px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.3px 30.2px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000!important;

}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.3px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="child-counseling.html"  ><img alt="img/logo-19053-black-1536x1518.png" src="img/logo-19053-black-1536x1518.png"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="navbar-collapse collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="ml-auto navbar-nav align-items-center d-flex"><li class="nav-item">
<a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5 nav-link" href="child-counseling.html" >Child Counseling</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5 nav-link" href="adolescents-counseling.html" >Adolescents Counseling</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5 nav-link" href="individual-counseling.html" >Individual Counseling</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5 nav-link" href="family-counseling.html" >Family Counseling</a>
</li>
<li class="dropdown nav-item">
<a class="dropdown-toggle v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5 nav-link" href="#" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">More</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="couples-counseling.html"  >Couples Counseling</a></div>
</li>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5 nav-link" rel=nofollow href="about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li><li class="nav-item">
<a class="btn v2f279d878e8059c8ff2123028bc7a233 btn-md" href="tel:866-766-4935" >Contact Us</a>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc.</h1>
<p>At Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc. one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc. and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/burnet-texas-mental-health-service/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc.. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc., address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc. follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc..</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc., which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc. has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc.'s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc. does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc.</br>
+18667664935</br>
205 S Pierce St Suite 2, Burnet, TX</br>
</br>
</br>
https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/burnet-texas-mental-health-service/</br>
info@peaceofmind4wellness.com</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="py-4 container pt-5" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>Peace of Mind Wellness & Family Counseling, inc.</p>
<p>Phone : +18667664935</p>
<p>Email : info@peaceofmind4wellness.com</p>
<p>Zip : 78611</p>
<p>Address : 205 S Pierce St Suite 2, Burnet, TX</p>
<p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://local.google.com/place?id=13670025510736045501&use=srp" >Google Business Website</a></p>
<p>Company Website : <a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/burnet-texas-mental-health-service/" >https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/burnet-texas-mental-health-service/</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>USEFUL LINKS</p>
<p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/individual-counseling/"  target="_blank">Individual Counseling</a></p><p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/child-counseling/"  target="_blank">Child Counseling</a></p><p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/adolescents-counseling/"  target="_blank">Adolescents Counseling</a></p><p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/family-counseling/"  target="_blank">Family Counseling</a></p><p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/couples-counseling/"  target="_blank">Couples Counseling</a></p></div><div class="col-lg-3"><p>LATEST BLOGPOSTS</p> 
 
<p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/build-strong-family-bonds-family-connections-counseling/"  target="_blank">Build Strong Family Bonds: Family Connections Counseling</a></p><p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/how-couples-counseling-in-santa-ana-can-help/"  target="_blank">How Couples Counseling in Santa Ana Can Help</a></p><p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="https://peaceofmind4wellness.com/why-mental-health-matters-for-all-ages/"  target="_blank">Why Mental Health Matters for All Ages</a></p><p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="v905fd56015c4e7a66140245a7469d8c5" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
<div class="col-lg-12">
<img class="img-fluid x215b9a4058c2f43277398a98099255d9" src="img/logo-19053-black-1536x1518.png" alt="">
</div>
</p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<div>
<p>Follow us</p>
<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/peace-of-mind-wellness-&-family-counseling-inc./" class="ce8df8403de2aa5fe62c0cb566cfb6b65 pinterest" ><i class="fa fa-linkedin"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.instagram.com/peaceofmind4wellness/" class="ce8df8403de2aa5fe62c0cb566cfb6b65 google-plus" ><i class="fa fa-instagram"></i></a>
</div>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
