<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en-US">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="Therapy For AnxietyBreaking Free from Anxiety’s GripLife with anxiety can often feel as if you’re navigating a complex labyrinth filled with worries, fears, and overwhelming thoughts. We don’t just understand your struggles – we’re dedicated to lighting your way out. We offer personalized, empathetic strategies to help you manage and lessen the grip of anxiety, providing practical tools to navigate your emotional terrain more effectively. Our mission is to alleviate your anxiety symptoms, enhance your overall wellbeing, and help you find calm amidst the storm.Child Therapy: Guiding Young MindsEvery child, at times, faces challenges that make their world seem like an overwhelming maze. As parents, watching your little one in distress is undeniably painful. At our center, we offer Child Therapy as a guiding light, transforming confusion into clarity and distress into empowerment.Couples Therapy: Navigating Relationship StormsEvery relationship, much like an ocean, has its ebbs and flows. When misunderstandings, trust issues, and conflicts storm in, the once harmonious dance between partners may waver. Our Couples Therapy stands as a beacon of hope during such times, guiding you both back to the shores of understanding and love.Depression Therapy: Journeying Through The FogBattling depression often feels like a solitary trek through an opaque mist of despair and fatigue. Know that in this journey, you’re not venturing alone. Our Depression Therapy offers a compassionate guiding hand, lighting your path with understanding and professional expertise.Therapy For Facing Addiction, Rediscovering HopeThe journey through substance abuse may seem like a lone, shadowed path, but no one should confront this challenge in isolation. With our Substance Abuse Therapy, you gain more than treatment – you gain a compassionate ally.Teen Therapy: Navigating The Waves Of AdolescenceAdolescence is an ocean of change, filled with waves of self-discovery, peer influences, and evolving emotions. While this journey is inherent to growth, navigating its tides requires guidance. That’s where our specialized Teen Therapy steps in.Therapy For Abuse: A Beacon Of HealingRecovering from any form of abuse is a courageous journey through intricate emotions and memories that can often be overwhelming. In these moments, what you deserve is a haven of understanding and validation – and that’s precisely what our Therapy for Abuse offers.Therapy For LGBTQ+ : Navigating The Tapestry Of Identity With PrideEmbracing one’s LGBTQ+ identity is a powerful journey of self-discovery, often met with societal challenges and the quest for acceptance. Your path deserves not just acknowledgment but also celebration, which is where our specialized therapy steps in.Trauma Therapy: Finding Light Beyond The ShadowsThe echoes of trauma can cast long, dark shadows over one’s life, turning vibrant landscapes into bleak terrains. But amidst the gloom, there lies the promise of dawn—a rebirth, resilience, and hope.">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logochannelinggrowth-removebg-preview1.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Roboto:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.btn-md{
padding: 14.9px 30px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.2px;
padding-right:7.8px;
padding-top:5.3px;
padding-bottom:4.5px;
}
*{
font-family: 'Roboto', sans-serif;
}
.y21a63bd3d0b54dd64d258eab49b49048{
background-color:#6bb600!important;
border-color:#6bb600!important;
color:#ffffff!important;
}
.wf7126ae39705019b49a3ad11a3e35873 a,.d3441453534f03a2dd11ce3df52d9cf46 a{
color:#0a0a0a!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000!important;

}
.d3441453534f03a2dd11ce3df52d9cf46 a{
font-size:16px;
}
.u53f7713d7ed3b326a46433b25689633b:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50.3px 50.3px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
footer{
background:#201f22;
color:#ffffff;
}
.d3441453534f03a2dd11ce3df52d9cf46 p,.d3441453534f03a2dd11ce3df52d9cf46 span,.d3441453534f03a2dd11ce3df52d9cf46 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.wf7126ae39705019b49a3ad11a3e35873 p,.wf7126ae39705019b49a3ad11a3e35873 a,.wf7126ae39705019b49a3ad11a3e35873 span,.wf7126ae39705019b49a3ad11a3e35873 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="anxiety-therapy.html"  ><img alt="img/logochannelinggrowth-removebg-preview1.jpg" src="img/logochannelinggrowth-removebg-preview1.jpg"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="navbar-collapse collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="d-flex navbar-nav align-items-center ml-auto"><li class="nav-item">
<a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e nav-link" href="anxiety-therapy.html" >Anxiety Therapy</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="child-therapy.html" >Child Therapy</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="couples-therapy.html" >Couples Therapy</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e nav-link" href="depression-therapy.html" >Depression Therapy</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item dropdown">
<a class="dropdown-toggle nav-link w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="#" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">More</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="substance-abuse-therapy.html"  >Substance Abuse Therapy</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="teen-therapy.html"  >Teen Therapy</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="therapy-for-abuse.html"  >Therapy For Abuse</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="therapy-for-the-lgbtq+-community.html"  >Therapy For The LGBTQ+ Community</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="trauma-therapy.html"  >Trauma Therapy</a></div>
</li>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" rel=nofollow href="about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li><li class="nav-item">
<a class="y21a63bd3d0b54dd64d258eab49b49048 btn btn-md" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/contact-us/" >Contact Us</a>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Channeling Growth Therapy</h1>
<p>At Channeling Growth Therapy one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Channeling Growth Therapy and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://channelinggrowth.com/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Channeling Growth Therapy. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Channeling Growth Therapy, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Channeling Growth Therapy follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Channeling Growth Therapy.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Channeling Growth Therapy, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Channeling Growth Therapy has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Channeling Growth Therapy's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Channeling Growth Therapy does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Channeling Growth Therapy</br>
+14083573201</br>
21 W Washington Ave suite 204, Sunnyvale, CA</br>
</br>
United States</br>
https://channelinggrowth.com/</br>
monet@channelinggrowth.com</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="container pt-5 py-4" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>Channeling Growth Therapy</p>
<p>Phone : +14083573201</p>
<p>Email : monet@channelinggrowth.com</p>
<p>State : United States</p>
<p>Zip : 94086</p>
<p>Address : 21 W Washington Ave suite 204, Sunnyvale, CA</p>
<p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://local.google.com/place?id=14878422555180371983&use=srp" >Google Business Website</a></p>
<p>Company Website : <a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/" >https://channelinggrowth.com/</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>SERVICES</p>
<p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/anxiety-therapy/"  target="_blank">Anxiety Therapy</a></p><p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/child-therapy/"  target="_blank">Child Therapy</a></p><p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/couples-therapy/"  target="_blank">Couples Therapy</a></p><p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/depression-therapy/"  target="_blank">Depression Therapy</a></p><p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/substance-abuse-therapy/"  target="_blank">Substance Abuse Therapy</a></p><p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/teen-therapy/"  target="_blank">Teen Therapy</a></p>
<p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/therapy-for-abuse/"  target="_blank">Therapy For Abuse</a></p>
<p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/therapy-for-the-lgbtq-community/"  target="_blank">Therapy For The LGBTQ+ Community</a></p>
<p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/trauma-therapy/"  target="_blank">Trauma Therapy</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3"><p>LATEST BLOGPOSTS</p> 
 
<p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/relationship-therapy-for-couples-in-california/"  target="_blank">Improving Relationships: The Benefits Of Couples Therapy In California</a></p><p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/what-to-talk-about-in-therapy-a-beginners-guide/"  target="_blank">What To Talk About In Therapy: A Beginner’s Guide</a></p><p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/unmasking-the-hidden-pain-signs-of-trauma-in-adolescence/"  target="_blank">Unmasking The Hidden Pain: Signs Of Trauma In Adolescence</a></p><p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="w7b262493d42ca4cb43f0a37e187ffd1e" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
<p><p><a aria-current="page" href="https://channelinggrowth.com/sunnyvale-california/">Service Area</a></p></p>
<div class="col-lg-12">
<img class="img-fluid u53f7713d7ed3b326a46433b25689633b" src="img/logochannelinggrowth-removebg-preview14.jpg" alt="">
</div>
</p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<div>
<p>Follow us</p>
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100094863440224" class="facebook e04ec94c13ba79d573a6077413f4a704c" ><i class="fa fa-facebook"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/monet-goldman-b85492285/" class="e04ec94c13ba79d573a6077413f4a704c pinterest" ><i class="fa fa-linkedin"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.instagram.com/channelinggrowththerapy/" class="e04ec94c13ba79d573a6077413f4a704c google-plus" ><i class="fa fa-instagram"></i></a>
<a href="https://twitter.com/channelingg" class="e04ec94c13ba79d573a6077413f4a704c twitter" ><i class="fa fa-twitter"></i></a>
</div>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
